是它吗
Is that it?
不是
No.
在那里
Oh, there it is!
不是
No.
在那里
There it is!
也不是
No.
今天可能是我人生中最酷的一天
This may be the coolest day of my life.
你现在看到的是
You're looking at the grand prize winner
史蒂夫牌芥末
of the Steve's Mustard
"赢得豪华轿车一天"竞赛的大奖得主
"Win a Limo for a Day" Contest.
我不得不吃掉了和我体重一样多的芥末酱
I had to eat my weight in mustard.
但我最终还是找到了有奖的那一罐
But I finally found the winning jar.
它来了它来了它来了
Here it is! Here it is! Here it is!
先生  早上好
Good morning, sir.
我是柯比  你今天的专属司机
I'm Kirby, your personal chauffeur for the day.
躲猫猫
Peek-a-boo!
这辆豪华轿车有超酷的芥末酱收藏
This limo has a fancy mustard collection!
我们去接我的队员吧  我们去商场吧
Let's go pick up my team. Let's go to the mall.
我知道有一个送葬仪式我们可以去参加
I know a funeral procession we can ride in.
大伙们  我知道你们对这辆林肯豪华轿车都很激动
Guys, guys, I know you're all excited about Lincoln's limo.
但我们先让他享受一会吧
But let's let him enjoy it for awhile first,
然后他会回来带我们去兜风
then he'll come back and take us for a ride.
对吧  小林肯  当然啦
Right, Linky? Sure.
我五点来接你们怎么样
How about I pick you all up at 5:00 o'clock
然后我们可以一起去打嗝汉堡店
and we can all go down to the Burpin' Burger?
耶
Yay!
你们都饿了吧  别观望了
Hungry, y'all? Look no further.
快来打嗝汉堡店
Come on down to Burpin' Burger
二级牛肉还有特殊调料
Grade B beef and special spice
翻过来吃味道更好
When it comes back up it's twice as nice
先生  您的高端出行体验现在开始
Your premium transportation experience begins now, sir.
为什么要叫我先生  叫我林肯
What's all this "Sir" Stuff? Call me Lincoln.
太好了  那我就放心了
Well, that's a load off.
我习惯给一些势利小人开车了
I'm used to driving around snobby guys.
所以我们现在去哪里  你有想去的地方吗
Hey, so where to? Anywhere you want?
我刚好知道一个地方
I know just the place.
两根吸管
Double straws?
第一根免费
First one's free.
第二根要付钱
You're payin' for that second one.
好好听的喇叭声
Sweet bimminy boo.
重要的客户来了
One side! Important customer!
欢迎来到菲利普的小店
Welcome to Flip's.
请享用您的免费饮料
Please enjoy your complimentary Flippy.
菲利普  你以前可从来没给过我免费的东西
Wow, Flip, you've never given me anything free before.
你以前可没有豪华轿车
Well, you never had a limo before.
我现在和一个坐着超豪华轿车的人在一起
I'm here with a very important limo rider
他刚刚才开进了镇里
who just rode into town.
告诉我们  你如何变得那么成功
Tell us--how did you get to be so important?
我喜欢你的豪华轿车
Say there, I like your limo.
你是怎么得到的
How did you obtain it?
呃  芥末酱
Uh, mustard.
你一定是芥末酱生意的继承人吧
Oh, you must be the heir to the mustard fortune.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
林肯·劳德  但我不是
Lincoln Loud. But I'm not the--
我是泰德伯爵  是绳球生意的继承人
I'm Lord Tetherbee, heir to the Tetherball fortune.
我正要去我私人的乡村俱乐部
I was just heading to my exclusive country club.
你要和我一起吗
Care to join me?
柯比  跟着那辆车
Kirby, follow that limo.
谢啦  柯比
Thanks, Kirby.
欢迎来到泰德乡村俱乐部
Welcome to the Tetherbee Country Club.
好舒服
Ooh, comfy.
当然了  现在我们去吃饭吧  老兄
Of course. Now shall we dine, old bean?
太好了  老  呃
Sounds good to me, old, uh...
萝卜
carrot?
我还能为你做什么吗  先生
Is there anything else I can get you, sir?
你不用叫我先生
Oh, you don't need to call me "Sir."
叫我林肯就行了
You can call me Lincoln.
听着  劳德
See here, Loud,
一个坐豪华轿车的人不会对那些仆人太好
a man in a limo doesn't act all chummy with the help.
这样只会让他们困惑
It only confuses them.
现在让我们像坐豪华轿车的有钱人一样  到镇上去逛逛
Now let's hit the town as limo people do.
豪华轿车来了
Limo! Limo coming through!
我从来不知道生活可以像这样
I never knew life could be like this.
现在已经四点四十五分了  劳德
I say, it's a quarter to five, Loud.
我们要不要在集市关门之前去逛逛
Shall we check on the markets before they close?
没关系  一般都是我妈妈去买东西的
That's okay, my mom usually does the shopping.
等下  四点四十五
Wait! A quarter to five?
我要去接我的姐妹们了
I'm supposed to pick up my sisters
还要带他们去打嗝汉堡店
and take them to to the Burpin' Burger.
打嗝汉堡店
The Burpin' Burger?
是啊
Yeah, you know...
二级牛肉还有特殊调料
Grade B beef and special spice
翻过来吃味道更好
When it comes back up it's twice as nice
听着  劳德  你是一个坐豪华轿车的人
Look here, Loud, you're a man in a limo.
你不能被人家看见
You can't be seen in some rat hole
在一个用身体机能命名的老鼠洞里
named after a bodily function.
这样是不对的
It's just not done.
可是我的姐妹们
But my sisters...
我们都有令人尴尬的亲戚们
We all have embarrassing relations.
我有一个二表弟  他坐公交车去上班
I have a second cousin who takes the bus to work.
你能想象吗
Can you imagine?
最重要的是我们不能被他们拖了后腿
The point is we can't let them hold us back.
来吧  老兄  现在是轿车帆航时间
Now come on, old bean, it's time for limo sailing.
风景太棒了
This view is incredible!
看  海豚
Oh, look, dolphins!
我要骑一只玩玩
I think I'll ride one.
等等我
Wait for me, old broccoli stalk.
我有惊喜送给你
I've got a little surprise for you.
今晚我们俱乐部有个盛会
We're holding a gala at the club tonight
来欢迎我们的新成员  就是你
to welcome our newest member--you!
-谢谢  老  呃  芹菜  -不客气
-Wow, thanks old, uh, celery? -Don't mention it.
你会和我们相处很融洽的
I think you'll fit in splendidly.
还有记着  只能"戴黑领带"
And remember, it's black tie only.
不穿裤子和其他的吗
No pants or anything?
你太搞笑了
Oh, Loud, you are a stitch.
抱歉  走错房子了
Sorry! Wrong house!
你去哪里了
Where have you been?
我们站在路边等了超过三个小时
We were standing on the curb for over three hours.
收垃圾的人差点要把拉娜扔到垃圾桶里去
The garbage guys literally tried to take Lana to the dump.
我真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
我一天都忙着和很有钱的泰德伯爵在一起
I had a busy day with the very wealthy Lord Tetherbee
我真的抽不开身
and I just couldn't get away.
我不敢相信你竟然和一个随便认识的有钱人
I cannot believe you have been hanging out
在一起玩了一天
with some random rich guy all day,
而不是带你们亲生姐妹们去打嗝汉堡店
instead of taking your own sisters to the Burpin' Burger!
一个坐豪华轿车的人不能被人家看见
A man in a limo can't be seen
待在一个用身体机能命名的老鼠洞里
in some rat hole named after a bodily function.
这样是不对的
It's just not done.
你不是一个坐在豪华轿车里的人
You're not a man in a limo.
你只是一个吃了一堆芥末酱的小孩
You're a kid who ate a bunch of mustard.
马上你的豪华轿车就要走了
As soon as your limo's gone,
你的幻想马上就要结束了
this little fantasy of yours is going to be over.
真的吗
Oh, really?
这就是为什么他们
Is that why they're making me a member
要给我一个记忆深刻的俱乐部之夜吗
of their club tonight?
恕我失陪
Now if you'll excuse me,
我要穿上我的正装
I need to put on my formalwear.
等着吧  林肯
You'll see, Lincoln.
你并没我高我们一等
You're no better than the rest of us.
没有高我们一等
No better than the rest of us?
她怎么敢这么说
How dare she?
我是一个很重要的人
I'm the important person
而且我要去一个很重要的地方
and I've got important places to be.
说到这个  为什么我们不动了
Speaking of which, why aren't we moving?
简直难以忍受
This is unacceptable.
你就不能想办法开过去吗
Can't you drive around this?
对不起  林肯  我也没办法
There's nothing I can do. Sorry, Lincoln.
别叫我林肯  叫我先生
Don't call me Lincoln. It's sir.
泰德是对的
Tetherbee was right.
如果你对于仆人太亲切
If you get too chummy with the help,
会让他们混淆的
it just confuses them.
我们直说吧  柯比
Let's keep this straight, Kirby.
我是一个坐豪华轿车的人
I'm the man in the limo.
你是开车的司机
You're the man driving the limo.
这是什么声音
And what's all this beeping?
这是计时器  先生
It's the timer, sir.
你的一天结束了
Your day is up.
你不是一个坐在豪华轿车里的人了
You're no longer a man in a limo.
什么
What?
你才是个笑话
Well, the joke's on you,
因为我顺走了你的一些芥末酱
'cause I took some of your mustard.
我现在在哪里
Where the heck am I?
乖狗狗
Nice puppies.
你们喜欢辣的酱料吗
Do you like spicy brown?
我更喜欢经典口味的
I'm more of a classic yellow fan, myself.
你才是个笑话
The joke's on you.
这些不是真的礼服鞋
These aren't real dress shoes.
这些是我用马克笔涂的运动鞋
They're sneakers I colored in with a marker.
你才是个笑话  因为  呃
But the joke's on you 'cause, uh...
我在开谁玩笑呢
Oh, who am I kidding?
我才是个笑话
The joke's on me.
嗨  泰德
Hello, Tetherbee?
是我  劳德  我来参加我的盛会了
It's me, Loud. I'm here for my gala.
劳德  你怎么了
I say, Loud, what happened to you?
主要是  你的豪华轿车呢
And, more importantly, what happened to your limo?
我不再拥有它了
I don't have it anymore.
没有他  你不可能加入这个俱乐部
Without a limo, you cannot possibly join the club.
这是不对的
It just isn't done.
可是  老  呃  豆芽
But, old, uh, sprout,
我以为我非常合适
I thought I fit in splendidly.
是啊  那是在你有豪华轿车的时候
You did--when you had a limo.
恕我失陪
Now, if you'll excuse me,
我有八百只林肯气球要戳爆
I have about 800 Lincoln balloons to pop.
现在我和一个曾经拥有豪华轿车的人在一起
I'm here with a former limo rider.
告诉我们  你是怎么从高处一下子跌落谷底的
Tell us, how does a man who rose so high sink so low?
我渐渐开始觉得我高人一等
Well, I started to think that I was better than everybody
而且我的行为像一个真混蛋一样
and acted like a real jerk.
可是事实上
But the truth is,
我只是一个吃了一堆芥末酱的小孩
I'm just a kid who ate a bunch of mustard.
我觉得应该是番茄酱
Looks more like ketchup to this reporter.
打嗝汉堡店  有了
Burpin' Burger? That's it!
我知道怎么弥补这一切了
I know how to fix everything.
我可以搭个车吗  搭这个新车吗
Can I get a ride? In the news van?
这是不可能的
It just isn't done.
拜托
Oh, come on.
你们还喜欢吃番茄酱啊
You guys like ketchup, too?
是林肯和他的酷炫芥末酱豪华轿车
Oh, it's Lincoln and his fancy mustard limo.
我以为他只能拥有一天
I thought he only had it for a day.
我们还得继续忍受他的态度吗
We've gotta put up with more of his attitude?
这不是我的豪华轿车
The limo's not for me.
是你们的
It's for you.
我对我昨天的行为感到非常抱歉
I'm sorry about the way I acted yesterday.
我不应该违背
I never should have broken my promise
我带你们去打嗝汉堡店的承诺
to take you guys to the Burpin' Burger.
你们饿了吗  别等了
Hungry, y'all? Look no fur--
轻点  他在认错呢  继续
Quiet! He's groveling. Proceed.
是啊  所以  我打电话给柯比道歉
Right, so, I called Kirby and apologized.
他答应再多载我们一次
He's agreed to give us one more ride.
我知道现在你们可能很生我的气
Now I know you're probably so mad at me
甚至不想去
that you don't even want--
我猜他们是原谅我了
I guess they forgive me.
欢迎来到打嗝汉堡店
Welcome to Burpin' Burger.
你们要点些什么
May I take your order?
亲爱的  来十一份汉堡和薯条
Eleven burgers and fries, love.
别忘了柯比的那份
Don't forget one for Kirby.
谢了  先生
Thank you, sir.
哦不  林肯
I mean, Lincoln.
唯一一件比做一个坐在豪华轿车里的人
The only thing better than being a man in a limo
更好的事情是一家人一起坐在豪华轿车里
is being a family in a limo.
嗨  劳德  很高兴看到你回到豪华轿车了
I say, Loud, it's good to see you back in a limo.
你为什么不甩了这些乌合之众
What say you ditch the riff-raff
回到俱乐部来呢
and come back to the club?
你知道吗  泰德
You know what, Tetherbee?
为什么不来点芥末酱
How about some mustard!
来搭配你那些蠢话
To go with that baloney!
你们都饿了吧  别再观望了
Hungry, y'all? Look no further.
快来打嗝汉堡店
Come on down to Burpin' Burger
二级牛肉还有特殊调料
Grade B beef and special spice
翻过来吃味道更好
When it comes back up it's twice as nice